{"data":[{"question":"People have a ________ for special occasions, such as a wedding, a funeral and a graduation.","a":"meal","b":"dance","c":"festival","d":"ceremony","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Ceremony: an important social or religious event, when a traditional set of actions is performed in a formal way.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"________ work is the work which is done the same way all the time.","a":"Routine","b":"Manual","c":"Mental","d":"Office","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Routine: the usual order in which you do things, or the things you regularly do.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"To ________ means to help someone remember.","a":"memorize","b":"reconsider","c":"remind","d":"suggest","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Remind: to make someone remember something that they must do.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"People ________ their money because they want their money to grow in value.","a":"save","b":"invest","c":"put away","d":"hide","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Invest: to buy shares, property, or goods because you hope that the value will increase and you can make a profit.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Henry will not be able to attend the meeting tonight because ________.","a":"he must to teach a class.","b":"he will have teaching a class.","c":"of he will teach a class.","d":"he will be teaching a class.","answer":"4","explain":"\n- If main clause is future tense, subordinate clause will be future tense or present tense.\u00a0\n- Because of + Noun\/noun phrase.\u00a0\n- Must + infinitive (without to).\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Alfred has not ________.","a":"never before lived alone","b":"ever lived alone before","c":"hardly live alone before","d":"lived lonelinessly in previous time.","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense: Have\/has + PP.\u00a0\n- Ever: a word meaning at any time; used mostly in questions, negatives, comparisons, or sentences with \"if\".\u00a0\n- Hardly: almost not.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The committee has met and ________.","a":"they have reached a decision.","b":"its decision was reached at.","c":"it has reached a decision.","d":"its decision reached.","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Collective nouns (team, staff, family, committee) may be either singular or plural depending on their use in the sentence.\u00a0\n+ Singular: when they act in a collective fashion or represent one group. \n+ Plural: when the members of the collective body act as individuals.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"John's score on the test is the highest in class. ________.","a":"He should study last night.","b":"He had studied hard.","c":"He must have studied hard last night.","d":"He must have to study hard last night.","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Must have pp: used to say you think something is very likely to be true or very likely to have happened.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"The chairman requested that ________.","a":"the members studied more carefully the problem.","b":"the problem was more carefulnessly studied.","c":"with more carefulness the problem could be studied.","d":"the members study the problem more carefully.","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + S + Infinitive (without to) + O.\u00a0\n- Passive voice: Require\/ suggest\/recommend ...+ that + BE +PP.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"},{"question":"Some snakes lay eggs, but others _____ birth to live offspring.","a":"give","b":"giving","c":"they give","d":"to have given","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Give birth (to somebody) if a woman gives birth, she produces a baby from her body.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"19","subcategorylv2":"34","type":"1"}]}